// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is an example of NLP?",
    answer: "Alexa",
    options: [
      "Automatic Washing Machine",
      "Alexa",
      "Self Driving Car",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the full form of A.I.",
    answer: "Artificial Intelligence",
    options: [
      "Artificial Intelligence",
      "Automatic Intelligence",
      "Ali baba Intelligence",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following is not a domain of A.I.",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Data",
      "Natural Language Processing",
      "Computer Vision",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which among the following is the top most important thing in data science? How is raw data processed ?",
    answer: "Question",
    options: [
      "Answer",
      "Question",
      "Data",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following language is the most used in data science ?",
    answer: "Python",
    options: [
      "Java",
      "C++",
      "Python",
      "C"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who is the father of A.I.?",
    answer: "John McCarthy",
    options: [
      "John McCarthy",
      "William",
      "Robert",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "_________ is a good way of performing experiments in data science?",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Have Replication",
      "Generalize to the problem",
      "Measure variability",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The available ways to solve a problem of state-space-search.",
    answer: "2",
    options: [
      "1",
      "4",
      "3",
      "2"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The application/applications of Artificial Intelligence is/are",
    answer: "All of the above",
    options: [
      "Expert Systems",
      "Gaming",
      "Vision Systems",
      "All of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the given language is not commonly used for AI?",
    answer: "LISP",
    options: [
      "PROLOG",
      "Python",
      "Perl",
      "LISP"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];